你并非生来注定为王  洛基
You weren't born to be king, Loki.
而是注定带来痛苦  苦难和死亡
You were born to cause pain and suffering and death.
前情提要
只有时间守护者避免我们
The Time-Keepers are all that stand
遭遇绝对灾难
between us and full-scale calamity.
时时刻刻
For all time.
永永远远
Always.
为什么把我关在这
Why am I locked in here?
你背叛了时管局
You were disloyal to the TVA.
你去过时间守护者的房间  他们不是真的
You were in the Time-Keepers' chambers. They weren't real.
-那又能改变什么  -那改变了一切
- And why does that change anything? - That changes everything!
你俩引起的关联事件
The nexus event the two of you caused,
不管是什么  都能摧毁这里
whatever that connection is, can bring this whole place down.
这对我来说是新体验  之前在拉曼蒂斯上时
This is new for me. Back on Lamentis...
如果你相信我  我可以帮你
I can help you if you trust me.
我们要找的人就在时间尽头的虚空之外
The person we're after is beyond The Void at the end of time.
那怪物就是他们的看门狗  保护着唯一的入口
That thing is just their guard dog protecting the only way in.
-那我们怎么越过看门狗  -我要用魅术控制它
- How do we get past the guard dog? - I'm gonna enchant it.
她相当有自信
She's pretty confident.
快
Go!
人人影视
原创翻译  双语字幕
翻译       恶作剧之草        杏仁斯嘉丽          Eunice
字幕组招新中
请访问 YYSubs.com
时间轴    树   念念   DA    后期   吉吉     校|监     草草
厉害  小豆子
Way to go, Tic Tac!
这样出拳才对
That's how you punch.
瓦坎达万岁
Wakanda forever!
不  你是该没听过我
No, you wouldn't have heard of me.
-你先别挂  -斗舞  哥们
- Let me put you on hold. - Dance-off, bro.
-他是我战友  -我可以和你耗一整天
- A friend from work. - I can do this all day.
-我知道  -我让你见识下什么叫猛
- Yeah, I know. - I'll show you ferocity.
更高  更远  更快啊  亲爱的
Higher, further, faster, baby.
我们有绿巨人
We have a Hulk.
我们要跳上那艘飞船离开这里
We're gonna jump on that spaceship and get out of here.
要一起来吗
Wanna come?
我们认为时间是单向的
We think of time as a one-way motion.
一个人的一小步
One small step for man...
他们怎么敢
How dare they!
我的梦
My dream...
我们为拥有和平而战
We have fought for the right to experience peace.
光荣使命
Glorious purpose!
受全世界女性的激励
Motivated by women throughout the world.
何为悲痛  不就是萦绕不去的爱吗
What is grief, if not love persevering?
我会崛起
I will rise.
睁开眼睛
Open your eyes.
洛基
第一季 第六集
你不打算叫我别踢门吗
Aren't you gonna tell me not to kick the door in?
说不说有什么关系呢
It never made a difference.
如果你觉得这样不好
Well, if you think it's a bad idea,
我更希望你说出来
I prefer you to speak your mind.
不  没什么想说的
No. Nothing to say.
那倒是头一遭
That'll be a first.
你还好吗
Everything okay?
嗯  就想缓缓
Yeah. Just need a moment.
嗯
Right.
-就是你一般...  -洛基  闭嘴
- It's just, you normally... - Loki, shut up.
你诞生之前  我就被删除了
I was pruned before you even existed.
我这辈子都在等待这一刻
I have been waiting for this moment my entire life.
我就需要点时间整理思绪  好吗
I just need a second to get my head straight, okay?
好  当然
Sure. Of course.
你们好
Hey, y'all.
又是你
You again?
欢迎来到时间尽头的大教堂
Welcome to The Citadel at the End of Time.
来吧
Come on.
恭喜
Congratulations.
你们为了来到这里经历了漫长的旅程
Y'all had an awfully long journey to get here.
他很钦佩
He's impressed.
你说谁
Who's impressed?
存留者
He Who Remains.
他是谁
And who is he?
他创造了一切  控制了一切
He created all and he controls all.
在尽头  就只有存留者
At the end, it is only He Who Remains.
他想跟你们做个交易
And he wants to offer you a deal.
他进行了一些创意调整
He's been making a few creative adjustments,
他已经盘算好
and he's worked it out
要怎么把你们放回时间线里
so we can reinsert both of y'all back into the Timeline
而不造成干扰
in a way that won't disrupt things.
"不造成干扰"
"Won't disrupt things"?
时管局可以继续进行他们重要的工作
The TVA can keep doin' its vital work
你们也可以过上你们一直想要的生活
and y'all can live the lives you've always wanted.
我们一直想要什么呢
And what have we always wanted?
别跟我装了  先生
Now, don't play coy with me, mister.
你清楚你怎么卷进这摊麻烦里的
You know how you got into this mess.
什么
What?
纽约之战  傻瓜
The Battle of New York, silly.
你对抗那些自以为是的复仇者
You versus those self-righteous Avengers.
你想赢吗
How would you like to win?
但不仅如此
But not just there.
你还可以杀了灭霸
You can kill Thanos.
你想要无限手套吗  那是你的了
You want the Infinity Gauntlet? Yours.
阿斯加德的王位  没问题
Throne of Asgard? No problem.
你呢  姑娘
What about you, missy?
那么多年来四处逃窜
All those years on the run.
绝望  孤独
Desperate, alone.
你想不想明早醒来
How would you like to wake up tomorrow
只有一辈子幸福的记忆
with just a lifetime of happy memories?
两个洛基在一个地方
Two Lokis in the same place.
我们俩
Both of us...
一起在一条时间线上
together on the Timeline.
很疯狂  但他能做到
It's crazy, but he could make it work.
这一切
All of it.
所有一切
Everything.
都完全如你们一直以来所愿
Exactly the way you've always wanted.
你们可以一起拥有
And you can have it all, together.
这是谎言
It's fiction.
我们现在要自己书写命运了
We write our own destiny now.
当然了  祝你们好运
Oh, sure you do. Good luck with that.
来吧
Come on.
时管局  正在下载
你好啊
Hey, there.
-你怎么才来  -抱歉
- What took you so long? - Sorry.
有事要解决
Some things had to get worked out,
但我正在下载你需要的文件
but I'm downloadin' the files you need now.
我要的不是这个
This isn't what I asked for.
我知道  但他觉得这个更有用
I know, but he thinks this'll be more useful.
谁
Who?
好好看吧
Happy readin'.
存留者
He Who Remains.
存在不了多久了
Not for much longer.
我们能确定他还活着吗
Are we sure he's even still alive?
真疯狂啊
This is wild.
你们俩  是同一个人
The two of you... ...same person.
有点有违自然  但是
I mean, it's a little unnatural. But...
疯狂
Wild.
存留者
He Who Remains.
她还那么喊我吗
She still calls me that?
吓人  是吧  但是
Creepy, right? But...
我喜欢
I like it.
来吧  来我办公室聊
Come on. Come on, let's talk in my office.
跟你们想的不一样吗
Not what you were expecting, hmm?
你只是个...人
You're just... A man.
血肉之躯
Flesh and blood.
-别说我令人失望  -不
- Don't tell me I'm a disappointment. - No.
就是更好杀了
Just a little bit easier to kill.
进来吧
Come on in.
一
One...
二
Two.
请坐吧
Please, take a seat.
洛基
Uh, Loki.
Loki.
两块糖
Two sugars.
我说了不要打扰我
I said I wasn't to be disturbed.
那你见到我肯定不会高兴了
Well, then you're not gonna be happy to see me.
他回来了
He's back.
如果有人能从虚空回来
If anyone was ever gonna make it back from The Void,
应该就是你了
I suppose it was gonna be you.
你懂的
Oh, well, you know,
一个人的虚空  对另一个人是小菜一碟
one man's Void is another man's piece of cake.
-你要删除我吗  -在主意好
- So, you're gonna prune me? - I like that idea.
但我在这方面的标准
But, you know, my standards might be
可能比你的要稍高点
a little bit higher in that area than yours.
对于亲密朋友什么的
You know, with close personal friends.
对不起  莫比乌斯
I'm sorry, Mobius.
我不能允许你阻碍我们的任务
I couldn't let you get in the way of our mission.
任务
Mission?
时间守护者是假的  我们都是时间异体
The Time-Keepers are fake. We're all Variants.
什么任务
What mission?
不能都是毫无意义的  所以我必须删除你
It can't have been for nothing. That's why I had to prune you.
追踪者D90  马上来我办公室
Hunter D-90 to my office, immediately.
嗯  抱歉  萝雯娜
Yeah. Sorry, Ravonna.
那不会有用的
That's not gonna work out the way you think it is,
我们知道你的秘密了
now that we know your secret.
你做了什么
What did you do?
警惕点  她就在附近
Stay alert, she's close.
俄亥俄州  弗里蒙特
封锁周边  我去抓她
Secure the perimeter. I've got her.
束手就擒吧  B15
Stand down, B-15.
你需要听我说
You need to listen to me.
-回头有时间让你说  -等等
- There'll be time for that. - Just wait.
这是怎么回事
What the hell is going on here?
伦斯雷尔法官
Judge Renslayer.
什么
What?
你是谁  你们来我学校干什么
Who are you? And what the hell are you doing in my school?
那不是伦斯雷尔法官
That isn't Judge Renslayer.
怎么回事
How?
我们有很多要谈的
We have a lot to talk about.
你的这段旅程很长  是吧
Been a long journey for you, hasn't it?
东躲西藏  历尽磨难
Lot of running, lot of pain.
你呢
And you...
你就是骑龙的跳蚤
You're a flea on the back of a dragon.
经历了一场大冒险
In for one hell of a ride.
但你还是一直抓住了
But you did manage to hang on.
这也算厉害吧
I guess that counts for something.
你恐怕不太明白现在的情况
I'm not sure you quite understand the situation.
你输了
You've lost.
我们找到你了
We found you.
拜托  当然了
Duh. Of course you did.
挥剑没中
A swing and a miss.
我们还要这么玩啊
So, we're still doing that, hmm?
我们先把这说明白吧
Let's get all this out of the way.
好
Okay.
找到了
Here we go.
你们不能杀我  因为
You can't kill me because
我已经知道会发生什么了
I already know what's going to happen.
看到了吗
See?
L.1130: 你恐怕不太明白现在的情况  你输了  我们找到你了
我: 拜托  当然了
这是雕虫小技
It's a parlor trick.
好吧
Okay.
你就不好奇
Don't you wonder
我怎么能在你刚要杀我前  闪开吗
how I'm able to get out of the way just before you kill me?
不  那是因为你有时空器
No. It's because of that little TemPad you have there.
嗯
Right.
但我怎么能已经在里面下载了
But how do I already have it loaded up
我需要知道的一切
with everything I need to know
从而避免被你俩杀掉呢
to keep from being killed by you two?
很简单
It's easy.
我什么都知道
I know it all.
什么都看过了
And I've seen it all.
你们在拉曼蒂斯上做的一切  我都看到了
Everything you guys did on Lamentis, I saw.
时管局不知道的那些事  我都知道
All the stuff the TVA didn't know about, I knew.
各种计谋  各种...
All the scheming, all the...
对话
...talking.
湖边的眼神
That little look by the lake.
对了  很动情  让人感动
Quite sentimental, very touching stuff, by the way.
不
No.
不  我们突破了你的小游戏
No, we broke out of your little game.
所以才来到了这里
That's how we got here.
不  错了
No, wrong.
你们走到这里的每一步
Every step you took to get here,
拉曼蒂斯  虚空
Lamentis, The Void,
都是我铺了路
I paved the road.
你们
You...
只是沿着路走
You just walked down it.
剩下的也都在这里
And I have the rest, uh, right here.
一切...
Everything that's, uh...
即将发生的事  只有一种结局
that's going to happen. There's only one way this can go.
-那为什么让我们来  -拜托
- Then why are we here? - Oh, come on.
你知道你要被旅途改变
You know you can't get to the end
才能走到终点
until you've been changed by the journey.
这件事  必须发生
This stuff, it needs to happen.
让我们进入最佳心态  好完成征途
To get us all in the right mindset to finish the quest.
-好吧  -嗯
- Right. - Right.
所以都是游戏
So, it's all a game.
都是...操纵
It's all... A manipulation.
有意思  你会这么想
Interesting, that your head would go to that.
茜薇
Sylvie,
你觉得你能信任他吗
you think you can trust this guy?
-别听他的  -"别听他的"
- Don't listen to him. - "Don't listen to him."
你觉得你能信任任何人吗
Do you think you're even capable of trusting anyone at all?
我觉得大家准备好听到真相了
I think people are ready to hear a little truth now.
比如时管局是个谎言
You know, like the TVA is a lie.
但如果是必要的谎言呢
But what if it's a necessary one?
有人创造了时间守护者
Someone created the Time-Keepers.
还创造了这里  给了我们使命
They created this whole place. They gave us all purpose.
我必须相信  那是有理由的
I have to believe they had a reason.
不  因为我见识过
No, because I've seen the horror
等待着被删除的人的恐怖
waiting for people when they get pruned
那绝没有必要性可言
and there's nothing necessary about that.
你知道我们如果不去删减时间线会怎样吗
You know what would happen if we didn't prune the Timeline?
-怎样  -混乱  死亡
- What? - Chaos. Death.
自由意志吗
Free will?
自由意志
只有一个人有自由意志  管事的那个
Only one person gets free will. The one in charge.
"跨越时间的朋友  检查到底的盟友"
"Friends across time, allies to the end."
-闭嘴  -多美的说辞
- Shut up. - That was so beautiful.
然后你送我去死  你是怎么了
And then you sent me to die. What happened to you?
没怎么  莫比乌斯  我没变
Nothing, Mobius. I didn't change.
你没变  你背叛了我
You didn't change? You betrayed me.
不  是你背叛了我
No, no. You betrayed me!
我很照顾你  替你担了风险
I looked out for you, hung my neck out for you,
你遭遇了信仰危机  就投向了那些时间异体吗
and you suffer a crisis of faith and turn to those Variants?
那么久的友谊
Eons of friendship.
你为了两个洛基就抛弃了一切
And you threw it all away on a couple of Lokis.
不  莫比乌斯  我没背叛你
No, Mobius. I didn't betray you.
我们不能夺走人们的自由意志  萝雯娜
We can't take away people's free will, Ravonna.
你不懂吗
Do you not see that?
-你干什么  -做我必须做的
- What are you doing? - What I need to do.
等等  别走
Wait, stop.
或许我们可以一起把它变得更好
Look, maybe we can build this into something better together.
对不起  莫比乌斯
I'm sorry, Mobius.
我不会让你走的
I'm not gonna let you go.
拜托  莫比乌斯
Please, Mobius.
即便有那个
Even with that...
你对我也不构成威胁
you're of no danger to me.
是吗
Is that what you think?
走着瞧吧
Let's see.
嗯  你说对了
Yep, you were right.
又是这样了
Back here again.
来吧
Go ahead.
你要去哪
Where are you gonna go?
寻找自由意志
In search of free will.
我理解你们对时管局工作的道德反感
I understand your moral objections to what the TVA does.
我的手段是充满欺骗
And my methods are deceptive.
但使命可不是欺骗
But the mission, it never was.
没有我  没有时管局
Without the me, without the TVA...
一切都会毁灭
everything burns.
那你还怕什么
Then what are you so afraid of?
我
Me.
你究竟是谁
And just who are you?
很多人给过我很多名字
Oh, I've been dubbed many names by many people.
统治者  征服者
A ruler, a conqueror.
存留者  混蛋
He Who Remains, a jerk.
但这并不单单是个名字的事
But it's... it's not as simple as a name.
很久以前  时管局建立前
Eons ago, before the TVA,
我的一个时间异体生活在31世纪的地球上
a variant of myself lived on Earth in the 31st century.
他是个科学家  他发现
He was a scientist and he discovered
宇宙是层层叠叠的
that there were universes stacked on top of his own.
同时
At the same time,
我们的其他版本也发现了这个奥秘
other versions of us were learning the same thing.
不用说  我们相互联系了
Naturally, they made contact.
在一段时间里  大家和平共处
And for a while, there was peace.
自恋  自我恭维的和平
Narcissistic, self-congratulatory peace.
"我喜欢你的鞋"  "我喜欢你的发型"
"I love your shoes." "I love your hair."
"鼻子挺好看"  "谢谢  伙计"
"Oh, man, nice nose." "Thanks, man."
等等
Et cetera.
他们分享科技和知识
They shared technology and knowledge.
用自己宇宙里最好的东西来改善其他宇宙
Using the best of their universes to improve the others.
但是
However...
不是我的所有版本
not every version of me
都那么  心地纯良
was so... so pure of heart.
对有些人  新世界就只意味着一件事
To some of us, new worlds meant only one thing,
有可征服的新领地
new lands to be conquered.
现实间的和平
The peace between realities...
爆发成了一场大战
...erupted into all-out war,
每个时间异体都在拼力保护自己的宇宙
each variant fighting to preserve their universe
同时毁灭其他宇宙
and annihilate the others.
这几乎终结了
This was almost the end...
一切和所有人  女士们先生们
...ladies and gentlemen, of everything and everyone.
然后时间守护者出现了  救了我们所有人
And then the Time-Keepers came along and saved us all.
阿门
Amen
不对
No. No.
不  这就是我们偏离常规的地方了
Nope, this is where we diverge from the dogma.
那第一个时间异体遇到了一个东西
That first variant encountered a creature
它是因现实的撕裂诞生
created from all the tears in reality,
它能吞噬时间和空间
capable of consuming time and space itself.
这东西
A creature...
你们都认识
you both know.
埃里奥斯
Alioth.
对了
Bingo!
我控制住了那野兽的力量  开始做实验
I harnessed the beast's power and began experimenting on it.
我把埃里奥斯武器化了
I weaponized Alioth
我终结了多元宇宙战争
and I ended... I ended the Multiversal War.
我把我们的时间线隔离出来后
Once I isolated our timeline,
就只需要打理好时间流
all I had to do was manage the flow of time
并防止出现新分支
and prevent any further branches.
因此  我创立了时管局
Hence, the TVA.
因此  我创造了时间守护者和高效的官僚机构
Hence, the Time-Keepers and a highly efficient bureaucracy.
因此  我打造了
Hence, ages...
长久的和谐
...and ages of cosmic harmony.
因此
Hence...
你们不客气
you're welcome.
你们是来杀魔鬼的  对吗
You came to kill the devil, right?
你们猜怎么
Well, guess what?
我保护了你们
I keep you safe.
如果你们觉得我是邪恶的
And if you think I'm evil, well,
等你们见到我其他时间异体再说吧
just wait till you meet my variants.
这就是开局
And that's the gambit.
是压抑的秩序  还是灾难性的混乱
Stifling order or cataclysmic chaos.
你们可能恨独裁者  但
You may hate the dictator, but something...
如果把他推翻  会有更糟的东西来填补空白
...far worse is gonna fill that void if you depose of him.
我活了千万辈子了
I've lived a million lifetimes.
我经历了一切情况
I've gone through every scenario.
这是唯一的办法
This is the only way.
时管局
The TVA,
很有效
it works.
或者你在撒谎
Or you're a liar.
或者我在撒谎
Or I'm a liar.
所以你要
So you just...
继续删除无辜的时间线吗
continue to prune innocent timelines?
是你们去
You two would.
有两个选择  一
There's two options! One...
你们杀了我  毁了这一切
you kill me and destroy all this,
到时就不仅是一个魔鬼了
so you don't just have one devil,
而是有无限个
you have an infinite amount.
或者
Or...
你们俩
you two.
你们俩来管事
You two run the thing.
你撒谎
You're lying.
你为什么要放弃控制权
Why would you give up being in control?
伙计
Buddy...
我累了
I'm tired.
我年纪大了
And I'm older.
比看上去年纪大
I'm older than I look.
这游戏属于年轻人  有欲求的人
This game is for the young, the hungry.
我经历了很多次
I've gone through a lot of scenarios...
想找合适的人选来接替我
trying to find the right person to take this spot.
原来合适的人选  是两个
It turns out that person came in two.
但绝对是你们俩
But it's definitely you two.
所以  不再撒谎了
So, no more lies.
你们杀了我  神圣时间线就会完全暴露
You kill me and the Sacred Timeline is completely exposed.
多元宇宙战争
Multiversal War.
或者  你们接手  回时管局去
Or you take over and return to the TVA
做个仁慈的统治者
as its benevolent rulers.
告诉员工他们是谁  以及为什么要做这个
Tell the workforce who they are and why they do what they do.
你把活生生的人的生活  当作游戏
You treated real people's lives like some kind of game.
不是针对谁  只是务实
It's not personal, it's practical.
我就觉得被针对了
It was personal to me.
长大吧  茜薇
Grow up! Grow up, Sylvie!
杀人犯  伪君子
Murderer! Hypocrite!
我们都是坏人
We're all villains here.
我们都干过可怕  糟糕  不堪的事
We've all done horrible, terrible, horrific things.
但现在  我们  你们
But now, we, you...
有机会为了好理由做那种事
have a chance to do them for a good reason.
我们刚刚
We just crossed...
过分界点了
the threshold.
我说谎了
So, I fibbed.
我之前说我知道
I fibbed earlier when I said
一切的走向是在撒谎  我...
I know how everything's going to go. I...
我知道  我之前只知道截止到某个时间点前的事
I know... I knew... ...everything up to a certain point,
那个时间点大概就是
and that point was about...
七八九十秒之前
seven, eight, nine, ten seconds ago.
但我现在不知道了
But now I have no idea.
不知道接下来的事会如何发展
No idea how the rest of this is going to go.
我很坦诚
I'm being candid.
那就这样了吗
So, that's it?
就这样了吗
That's it?
时间尽头就是这样吗
This is what happens at the end of time?
你就打算坐在那里享受自由
And now you're just gonna sit there with all that freedom and...
让我们决定你的命运吗
let us decide your fate?
对
Yes!
对  最坏能怎样呢
Yes! Yes! What's the worst that can happen?
你们要么就...
You either...
接手  我的毕生事业得以继续
take over and my life's work continues
要么你们就给我胸口来一刀
or you plunge a blade in my chest
无限多的我
and an infinite amount of me...
开启另一场多元宇宙战争
start another Multiversal War.
我最终又会回到这里
And I just... end up right back here anyways.
这就是轮回转世
Reincarnation, baby.
不  那只是另一个谎言
No, it's just another lie.
另一个操控伎俩
Another manipulation.
不是谎言
No lie.
不是操控伎俩
No manipulation.
我好喜欢这个
I love this.
我喜欢这种诚实
I love... all this honesty.
感觉是一个全新的开始
Feels like a fresh start.
该死...
Oh, holy...
-你干什么  -茜薇  等等
- What're you doing? - Sylvie, hang on a moment.
我们好好谈谈
Let's just talk about it.
我们不如先完成我们要做的事  杀了他
Well, how about we finish what we started and kill him?
-如果他说的是实话呢  -那又怎样
- What if he's telling the truth? - So what?
-我相信他  -你相信什么
- I believe him. - You believe what?
有无数的妖怪会出现在这里
That a bazillion boogeymen is gonna turn up
就因为我们给了人们自由意志
just because we give people free will?
-他是个骗子  洛基  -我也是
- He's a liar, Loki. - So am I.
我觉得他没撒谎  在这件事上没有
And I don't think he was lying. Not about that.
疯狂吗  没错  但他可能说的是实话
Insane? Yes. But maybe he was telling the truth.
快点吧  时间线已经开始分支了
Better hurry. Timeline's already branching.
-你想说什么  -我们好好想想
- So, what are you suggesting? - That we think about it.
有什么可好好想想的
And what precisely is there to think about?
你没听他说的吗
Weren't you listening to what he was saying?
这就是开局
That's the gambit.
除掉独裁者  填满虚空的是什么
Remove the dictator and what fills the void?
你想要王座
You want the throne?
不是的  不
No, that's not it. No.
-我不相信你  -茜薇  宇宙平衡了
- I don't believe you. - Sylvie, the universe is in the balance,
我们所熟知的一切  一切
everything we know to be true. Everything.
我知道时管局伤害了我俩
I know the TVA has hurt us both.
但如果干掉他以后
But what if by taking him out,
可能会释放出更难对付的东西呢
we risk unleashing something even worse?
我只想说  我们再稍微想一想
All I'm suggesting is we just take a minute to think about it.
我真心向你保证  我不是为了王座
I promise you from my heart this isn't about a throne.
我怎么能信任你
What was I thinking trusting you?
一切都是骗局吗
Has this whole thing been a con?
真的吗
Really?
你就这样看我吗
That's what you think of me...
发生了这么多之后
after all this time?
好啊  为什么不呢
Sure. Why not?
邪恶洛基的宏伟计划要实现了
Evil Loki's master plan comes together.
你根本从不信任我  对吗  那意义何在
Well, you never trusted me, did you? What was the point?
你不明白吗  这比我们的经历都更重要
Can't you see? This is bigger than our experience.
我们对此的看法为什么不同
Why aren't we seeing this the same way?
因为你无法相信别人
Because you can't trust...
我也不可信赖
and I can't be trusted.
看来我们有麻烦了
Then I guess we're in a pickle.
茜薇  等等
Sylvie, wait.
等一下
Wait.
茜薇  茜薇
Sylvie. Sylvie.
也许他在说谎  也许他没有
Maybe he's lying! Maybe he's not.
弄错的代价太大了
The cost of getting this wrong is too great.
好吧  动手吧
Fine. Do it.
杀了我  夺取你的王位
Kill me. Take your throne.
不
No.
茜薇  住手  住手
Sylvie, stop. Stop.
住手
Stop.
我经历过你现在的处境
I've been where you are.
我也感受过你现在的心情
I've felt what you feel.
别问我是怎么知道的
Don't ask me how I know.
我只知道
All I know...
我不想伤害你
is I don't wanna hurt you.
我不想要王位
I don't want a throne.
我...
I just...
我只希望你平安无事
I just want you to be okay.
但我不是你
But I'm not you.
难以置信
Incredible.
你不打算求饶吗
Aren't you gonna beg for your life?
我是可以求饶
Um, could, could.
我们很快会再见
I'll see you soon.
现在无法回头了
No turning back now.
谁说要回头了
Who said anything about turning back?
"时时刻刻"
"For all time."
"永永远远"
"Always."
收到  正赶往军械库  长官
Copy. Reporting to the armory, sir.
光是这个单位就有63条时间分支吗
That's, what, 63 new branches in this unit alone?
他是要我们任由它们全产生分支吗
Does he want us to just let them all branch?
我们现在要如何阻止它
At this point, how are we gonna stop it?
我们无法阻止
We can't!
什么
What?
你说什么
What'd you say?
已经结束了  莫比乌斯
It's done, Mobius.
我们犯了严重错误
We made a terrible mistake.
-什么结束了  -什么
- What's done? - What?
我们解放了时间线
We freed the Timeline.
我们在风暴的另一边找到了他
We found him beyond the storm.
一座在时间尽头的城堡
A Citadel at the End of Time.
他非常可怕  他策划了一切
He's terrifying. He planned everything.
他见识过一切  无所不知
He's seen everything. He knows everything.
事情很复杂  好吗
It's complicated. Okay?
-好  -但有人要来了
- Right. - But someone is coming.
一个极度危险人物的
Countless different versions
无数个不同版本
of a very dangerous person.
他们都是来开战的  我们需要准备迎战
And they're all set on war. We need to prepare.
冷静点  你是分析师  对吗
Take it easy. You're an analyst, right?
-你是哪个部门的  -什么
- What division are you from? - What?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
你是谁  你叫什么
Who are you? What's your name?
马上派出地面部队  档案室
Boots on the ground now. Archives.
你是谁
Who are you?
洛基·劳菲森
洛基将于第二季回归